SAMPURNA GAUTAM

Software Developer

ABOUT ME

Recent graduate of Business Information Technology from Haaga-Helia with a focus on software development who is highly motivated and full of can do attitude. Interned at Beesh where i worked with individuals from different cultures to bring a change in the field of sex education to kids through technology. I am from Nepal, but i have traveled around Europe for the past for 3 years and now settled down in here looking for professional employment. With my travel experiences I've met a variety of people and I can say with certainty that one of my strongest suits is my ability to understand and co-operate with different types of people.

Contact

(+358) 0401524199

sampad789@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sampurna-

gautam

Git Hub: https://github.com/sampad789

Education

Bachelor in Business Information Technology

Hagga-Helia University of Applied Sciences 2016-2021

Focus on Software Engineering

Refrences

- Yazeed Maswadeh(CEO)-Beesh oy
- +358407122317/ Yazeed@beesh.fi
- Johanna Joutsimaki(ex-Manager)
- +358400432664/johanna.joutsimaki@gmail.com
 - Parimal Giri (Daily operations officer & manager)-Momotoko
 - +358449762783 / giri@momotoko.com

Work Experience

DEVELOPER INTERN

Beesh OY | Helsinki, Finland | 2021-2021

- Website development
- Development of technical specifications and plans
- Building stable and maintainable Codebase using react.
- Maintaining and the updating preexisting website and databases.
- Code reviews and experience of work in multicultural environment.

Restaurant Worker

Momotoko | Helsinki ,Finland | 2019-Present

- Customer Service
- Training Staff
- Opening and Closing Duties
- Stock Management
- Handling Till

Skills

- React
- React Native
- Node js, Express.js
- Javascript
- Spring, Maven, Thymeleaf
- HTML,CSS3,BootStrap,Material UI
- Git, Databases, Maria Db, Mongodb
- Agile Methodology

Mentionables

JUNCTION 2018 PARTICIPANT

One of the biggest hackathons in Finland

Made a React native app that supported instant Top up of balance in the phone to charge electric vehicle for a company called Ensto.

STUDENT PROJECT FOR MARKETING

CLINIC

Finnish Company's Project

Made a React app with material UI ,redux, hapi and Maria DB (4 month project with 15+ students)